



📛 6th April 2000, Cracow



790 701 077



milenajas@gmail.com



https://github.com/MilenaJasiolek



in @ Linkedin

I am studying Master's degree in Neurobiology. I am an ambitious person who is always looking for new challenges. I try to improve my knowledge in topics that interest me, e.g. I had a lot of courses in the field of clinical trials, and besides, I am interested in programming I am trying my hand at creating websites.

MILENA

JASIOŁEK

While working as a Data Annotator, I had the opportunity to develop analytical skills and gain experience in data analysis and ensuring quality. My work primarily revolved around annotating and analyzing data using MS Excel spreadsheets. This environment allowed me to refine my analytical skills and precision, which are crucial in the role of an application tester. Through practical involvement in Quality Assurance (QA) processes, I acquired attention to detail, the ability to spot errors, and a systematic approach to data testing. This heightened my awareness of the significance of quality in the final product and honed my meticulous approach to analyzing and identifying potential issues.

EDUCATION

Jagiellonian University

Neurobiology Masters

2022 - June 2024

pyogenes.

2018 - 2022

Biotechnology Bachelor degree

topic of bachelor's thesis: Study of the formation of biofilms by clinical strains of the species Streptococcus pneumoniae and Streptococcus

SKILLS

- SQL, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, SCSS, Git, Webpack
- Computer skills, including Office
- English C1
- Deutsch A1.2
- Driving license cat. B

TRAINING AND **COURSES**

- June 2021 Good Clinical Practice (GCP)
- June 2021 Clinical Trials application in practice (GCP)
- February 2021 Basic about clinical trials
- June 2023 present **Programming Education - Samurai Programming -**(including Basics of Web Development, Intermediate Front-end, JavaScript Programming, React from scratch theory and practice)

HOBBIES

- Reading books
- Board and computer games
- · Gym, traveling
- Crocheting

WORK HISTORY

• september 2022 - present

Maj Instytute of Farmacology PAN - Department od Neurobiology (master's student)

Participation in the analysis of biochemical and molecular changes in the mouse brain caused by the use of zinc deficiency and stress, e.g. Western Blot, electrophoresis, analysis of behavior.

• december 2021 - december 2023

Epinote (Data Annotator)

Annotation and data analysis, QA. Work based mainly on MS Excel spreadsheet. Raising competences in the field of analytical skills and

august 2021 - september 2021

OMICRON - Ośrodek Genomiki Medycznej (trainee)

Working with DNA and RNA genetic material. Isolations, PCR, qPCR, RT-PCR, Western Blot, concentration measurements

• march 2021 - september 2021

Bobole - online shop (office worker)

Fulfillment of orders, inventory management and current administrative matters. In addition, handling the cash register, accepting returns, contact with the client and MS Office.

• june 2018 - september 2018

Miejskie Przedsiębiorstwo Komunikacyjne S.A. w Krakowie (Specialist)

Handling applications, accepting and verifying them. Ongoing contact with the client and working with documentation for archiving.